mpmschoolsupplies.com 2018-09-01

# Privacy Policy – SupplyMe

**In a nutshell:** Our goal is to collect as little information as possible to process your orders and only use the information we collect for that purpose.

We are committed to protecting your privacy and securing your personal information. So committed, in fact, that we worked with our payment processor to ensure that we **never** have access to your full credit card information, including credit card number and security code.

Please take a moment to read the details of our Privacy Policy below to learn more about our information practices, including what type of information is gathered, how the information is used and for what purposes, to whom we disclose the information, and how we safeguard your personal information. By accessing or using our Sites, you acknowledge that you have read and understand this Privacy Policy. Further, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy, please discontinue use.

## Why we collect personal information

We collect your personal information for the purpose of filling orders you place on our Sites. We also collect your personal information because it helps us deliver a superior level of customer service. It enables us to give you convenient access to our products and services and focus on categories of greatest interest to you. In addition, your personal information helps us keep you posted on the latest product announcements and special offers that you might like to hear about.

## What information we collect

In order to provide you with a quick, convenient, personalized shopping experience, we collect and store the following information:

  * **Personal information** , such as your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, and billing information when you register for a SupplyMe Account or otherwise voluntarily provide such information, such as when making payments or corresponding with us.
  * **Cookies** and other technologies to enhance your online experience and to learn about how you use our Sites in order to improve the quality of our services.
  * **Usage information** , including the URL, IP address, browser type and language, and the date and time of your request is automatically recorded by our servers when you visit our Sites.

All above personal information collected will be retained as part of your records, in order to provide you with improved and customized service.

When you access your online account, make any payments, send us e-mails, or conduct other transactions with us, we may ask you to provide personally identifiable information to us. When this personal information is supplied to us, we will make commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the privacy of your information. However, at times, it may be necessary to disclose personal information to unaffiliated companies/vendors for the limited purpose of completing your transaction, postal and e-mail delivery, customer service, or data analysis.

## How we use your personal information

We collect and use your personal information to operate and improve our Sites and deliver the services or carry out the transactions you have requested. These uses may include providing you with more effective customer service; making our Sites or services easier to use by eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information; performing research and analysis aimed at improving our products, services and technologies; and displaying content and advertising that are customized to your interests and preferences.

Our Sites market to visitors through the use of remarketing. Third-party vendors, including Google, show our ads on sites across the Internet and use cookies to serve our ads based on a visitor's past visits to our Sites. If you wish to opt out of Google's use of cookies, you may do so by visiting the [Ads Preference Manager](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/).

We also use your personal information to communicate with you. We may send certain mandatory service communications, such as welcome letters, invoices, shipping notifications, billing reminders, information on technical service issues, and security announcements. All non-mandatory communication is opt-in and will include a method to unsubscribe.

All personal information provided to us shall remain the property of SupplyMe. The information collected, managed and stored by us may be retained indefinitely for the above-mentioned purposes.

## Sharing Information

We may employ third party companies to perform functions on our behalf. These functions may include order fulfillment, package delivery, marketing assistance, postal and e-mail delivery, customer service, data analysis, and credit processing. The third parties we contract for these purposes have limited access to your personal information and may not use it for other purposes.

As our business continues to evolve, we may acquire or sell business units or subsidiaries. Customer information is one of the business assets that would be transferred in these types of transactions. In such a situation, your personally identifiable information would only be used in a manner consistent with our pre-existing Privacy Policy.

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by federal, state and local laws or regulations and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Sites. In such situations, we will make commercially reasonable efforts to disclose only the personal information required.

## How we protect your personal information

In an effort to protect your information, we **never** have access to your full credit card information, including credit card number and security code. We also don't require passwords to create an account or to login.

On all web pages where personal information is required, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption to encrypt your information while in transit over the internet. To make purchases from our Sites, you must use an SSL-enabled browser, such as Chrome, Internet Explorer, Edge, Firefox, or Safari. Doing so protects the confidentiality of your personal and credit card information while it’s transmitted over the Internet.

Please be aware that payments may be made using a third party company. As such, personal financial information may be collected and stored by this third party company. If such payment methods are used, please take time to review these third party company policies as well, since we are not responsible for the privacy policies of these third party companies.

## Children's Online Privacy

Protecting children on the Internet is very important to us. For that reason, we do not intentionally collect information on our Sites from those we actually know are under 13. Parents can be proactive and limit web site access to their children by installing filtering software.

The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) protects children under the age of 13 from the online collection of personal information. Learn more about COPPA at the Federal Trade Commission's web site for children's privacy at <http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/edcams/kidzprivacy/index.htm>.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

We will occasionally update this privacy statement to reflect changes in our services and customer feedback. When we post changes to this Statement, we will revise the "document updated" date at the top of this Statement. If there are material changes to this Statement or in how we will use your personal information, we will notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes prior to implementing the change or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to periodically review this statement to be informed of how we are protecting your information.
